What?!
I'm back down to nine friends!
(Sheldon:)Make it eight.
I'm sick of Wolowitz, too!
(Leonard:)I don't understand.
(Leonard:)All you've done since you discovered
this stupid element was complain.
I was trying to make you happy!
(Sheldon:)By taking away
my only claim to fame?
(Sheldon:)Well, if you wanted
to make me happy,
(Sheldon:)you could have told me a joke.
(Sheldon:)Or shown me a cute video
of a koala and an otter
(Sheldon:)becoming unlikely friends.
(Leonard:)There is no winning with you.
(Leonard:)And koalas and otters
don't even live near each other!
(Sheldon:)That's what makes
their friendship unlikely!
Hey!
What's with all the yelling?
(Sheldon:)Leonard disproved my element.
(Sheldon:)Now all the attention
is going to go away.
(Penny:)Oh, that's great.
You must be thrilled!
That's it!
I'm down to seven friends.
(Penny:)He's counting Hobbits
and superheroes, right?
(Sheldon:)When I thought the element was real,
I didn't want it.
(Sheldon:)But now that Leonard
made it not exist,
(Sheldon:)I want it more
than anything in the world.
(Ira:)The element
never existed.
(Leonard:)I didn't take it away,
science took it away.